When life gives you a second chance, don't do it for
yourself. Do it for everyone you love.
Big George Foreman is a history, drama film directed by George Tillman Jr..
Fueled by an impoverished childhood, George Foreman channeled his anger into becoming an Olympic Gold medalist and World
Heavyweight Champion, followed by a near-death experience that took him from the boxing ring to the pulpit.
But when he sees his community struggling spiritually and financially, Foreman returns to the ring and makes history by
reclaiming his title, becoming the oldest and most improbable World Heavyweight Boxing Champion ever.
George Foreman, played by Khris Davis.
Doc Broadus, played by Forest Whitaker.
Muhammad Ali, played by Sullivan Jones.
Roy Foreman, played by Deion Smith.
Howard Cosell, played by Matthew Glave.
Desmond, played by John Magaro.
Big George Foreman: The Miraculous Story of the Once and Future Heavyweight Champion of the World (or simply Big George Foreman) is a 2023
American biographical sports drama film on the life of world heavyweight boxing champion George Foreman, played by Khris Davis.
It was directed by George Tillman Jr.
and also stars Jasmine Mathews, John Magaro, Sullivan Jones,
Lawrence Gilliard Jr., Sonja Sohn and Forest Whitaker.
Development on Big George Foreman began in 2021 and after several production delays, filming
took place on a budget of $32 million from February to March 2022 in New Orleans.
The film was released theatrically by Sony Pictures Releasing
on April 28, 2023, and grossed $6 million.
The film explores themes of adultery, sports, 1970s, texas, biography.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.